[{
        "no": 1,
        "question": "1 + 1 = ?",
        "choice": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "no": 2,
        "question": "2 + 2 = ?",
        "choice": ["1", "3", "4", "5"],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "no": 3,
        "question": "3 + 3 = ?",
        "choice": ["6", "2", "3", "4"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "no": 4,
        "question": "2 x 2 = ?",
        "choice": ["1", "4", "6", "8"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "no": 5,
        "question": "3 x 3 = ?",
        "choice": ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "no": 6,
        "question": "12 / 3(2+2) = ?",
        "choice": ["1", "2", "8", "16"],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "no": 7,
        "question": "B.E. 2018 is A.D. ?",
        "choice": ["2561", "2560", "1475", "1476"],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "no": 8,
        "question": "A.D. 2018 is B.E. ?",
        "choice": ["2561", "2560", "1475", "1476"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "no": 9,
        "question": "B.E. 1995 is A.D. ?",
        "choice": ["2538", "2539", "1451", "1452"],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "no": 10,
        "question": "A.D. 1995 is B.E. ?",
        "choice": ["2538", "2539", "1451", "1452"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "no": 11,
        "question": "What color of tometo ?",
        "choice": ["red", "blue", "green", "yellow"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "no": 12,
        "question": "What color of watermelon ?",
        "choice": ["red", "blue", "green", "yellow"],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "no": 13,
        "question": "What color of water watermelon ?",
        "choice": ["red", "blue", "green", "yellow"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "no": 14,
        "question": "What choice is not day ?",
        "choice": ["moonday", "tuesday", "wednesday", "thursday"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "no": 15,
        "question": "What color of Sunday in Thailand ?",
        "choice": ["red", "blue", "green", "yellow"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "no": 16,
        "question": "What color of Monday in Thailand ?",
        "choice": ["red", "blue", "green", "yellow"],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "no": 17,
        "question": "What color of Tuesday in Thailand ?",
        "choice": ["cream", "blue", "pink", "yellow"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "no": 18,
        "question": "What color of Wednesday in Thailand ?",
        "choice": ["cream", "red", "green", "yellow"],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "no": 17,
        "question": "What color of Thursday in Thailand ?",
        "choice": ["red", "pink", "purple", "orange"],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "no": 18,
        "question": "What color of Friday in Thailand ?",
        "choice": ["red", "blue", "green", "yellow"],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "no": 19,
        "question": "What color of Saturday in Thailand ?",
        "choice": ["red", "pink", "purple", "orange"],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "no": 20,
        "question": "What color of Saturday in Thailand ?",
        "choice": ["red", "pink", "purple", "orange"],
        "answer": 3
    }





]